[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary mayhem erupting around you, your story, this movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, it's a bit surreal for sure because, I mean, I think controversial more than notorious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What is the real message you want to get out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, I mean, I guess for me, I -- it's important that the movie is viewed the right way certainly as a cautionary tale.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "And what did make you feel like to see DiCaprio do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "It was amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "How much time did you spend with Leo DiCaprio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I spent a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leo DiCaprio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "You know, countless hours, you know, hundreds of hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Hundreds of hours in his company?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Yeah, or hundred plus hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "And how did you find him and how did he find you when you were just interacting together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Oh, either, you know, by telephone in my house or his house or out somewhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "When you watched the movie, what did you feel about the reality because only you would know really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "You know it was shocking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "In a good or bad way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "In a -- in a good way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "A female employee shaved her head for $10,000 in front of the paying morbid (ph) stuff, true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "True.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$10,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "To get breast implant, she shaved her head for $10,000?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Yes, yes and if they -- I guess that the philosophy was, you know, her hair will grow back and then it would all be perfect in six months.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$10,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "$50?", "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, you become numb and that's what happened with insanity and all the sort of stuff that you do where what seems amazing at first becomes complex after a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$50"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I wasn't there at that time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "But you heard it happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "After I left, yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Your number two portrayed in the movie by Jonah Hill ate a live goldfish that belong to a Sratton Oakmont, the firm employee, did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "It happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sratton Oakmont"], "PERSON": ["Jonah Hill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "You saw him do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Danny"]}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "So the real-life guy is who really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "It's a guy named Danny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 186, "question": "But did Danny eat the goldfish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "He ate the goldfish though, yes, and he has publicly admitted that and ...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Danny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "It kind of nadir (ph) of croaking (ph) excess, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "It's about who can go the furthest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I think it -- I think that sort of behavior isn't just endemic to Wall Street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "NNS", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Did you have a chimpanzee in the office handing out mail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Not mail because they have like -- people had pets in the office.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "You kind of thinking this is perfectly normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "ELFORT: I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Can you give me a clue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "It had to do with in act of sexual deprave view.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Well, how would you categorize it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "A bit of embarrassment, and you know, putting on brave face maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Do you feel shame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Not -- it's not -- shame is the wrong word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "When was it you realized you have this ability to sell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "The first time is -- it really started in the meat business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "They want a dental school and you bail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yeah, I bailed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Because I have apparently guys and you couldn't make -- you couldn't rich too, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I, yeah -- I've really, you know, I always want to be rich.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "You actually made yourself bankrupt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "``", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Do you think you missed this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "And I'm like, \"This is it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "When you say over meaning was it -- didn't the firm went on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Yes, the firm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "They cure cancer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Besides they cure cancer that's the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "And what do you realize in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, you know, one of the important distinctions I think is the people to know you, especially young people, is that in the movie when I walk into the firm and I get my first look at it, and I sit down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Is that what happened in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "No, not quite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "When did you realize it wasn't what it seemed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "About two -- I would say about a month in -- I totally got what's going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "And is that the ethical moment for you when you crossed the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "It was -- there was a series of moments.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CD", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBG", ",", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "When it became as big firm, Stratton Oakmont, and you were making millions and millions and millions, how much of it do you think -- looking back of it, and be completely honest here because you have been about many things, how much of it was legal and how much of it was illegal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "JJS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I would say 90 percent was legal in terms of the data it operates, 95 probably, but the five percent was incredibly destructive, and disgusting, and poisoned, everything else.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stratton Oakmont"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "And you knew that was all happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "PDT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Why did you become this art criminal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, I think that what happened was is that when you get into this section of Wall Street, it's very easy just sort of rationalizing what you're doing and I rationalized each of my actions one step at a time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And what's the easy answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Is that they didn't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Did you lose your soul completely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "You know, I think that's -- it's hard to say because I think that I got to a point in my life where I was probably about as awful as a person as I was capable of being and still walking around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Are you surprised more people in Wall Street haven't gone to prison since the financial crash that we all went through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "As of now, you've paid back how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "About 12.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you have any expectation or hope you'll ever get to pay them all back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Is that not right anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "That's not right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Was there ever the case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Yes, for I was on probation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "But are you continuing to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I'm giving 100 percent of both books, everything, and the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Why is that not true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Because we we're calling rich people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "That you were deliberately...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Well, some of them did, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I don't know anyone who lost their life savings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "... in some cases, having their lives completely turned upside down?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I think it's terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Have you met one of your victims?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I have not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "No one just sought me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Why haven't you sought them out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "You know, I don't want to intrude anybody's life and you know...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "But have you ever seen them as human beings or it's part of the issue with the kind of culture that we see in the movie that actually in the end you become suddenly dehumanized?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Oh Piers, I think it's a very good point you're bringing up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "If I found a few of your victims, would you come and see them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "If you found them, oh yeah, sure I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Possibly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP"], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What about somebody losing half their life savings like the guy I read out, Peter Springsteel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Well, again I..", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter Springsteel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "My parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What else did she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No judgment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "No criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Your father, what did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Similar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "How best to deal with the feelings you may have of the old Jordan Belfort?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "You know it's -- I think for me I'm in a place in my life right now where my -- the business I'm in right now where I go around the world doing seminars, and sales training, and motivations, stuff like that, and entrepreneurship -- I know in my heart that what I'm doing is pure and it's great and it's empowering.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jordan Belfort"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "And as scene in the movie, this memorable scene where Leo DiCaprio taking too many quellos (ph) and just basically disintegrating before our very eyes which happened, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "An incredible acting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leo DiCaprio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Was it the balloon going up, being arrested, was it the court case, was it going to prison, was it the first night in prison, what was the absolute lowest moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I think the lowest moment for me was not getting arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Bad father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "I know I was an amazing father and I'm proud of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Always an amazing father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Oh, I mean listen I had a -- I got sober when my daughter was three and my son was one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "What's your relationship with them like now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I was really, really close.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "What did they think of the movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "It was -- and it's good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Did you hit her at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "Well, we had a struggle on the stairs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "When you took your ex-wife and your kid to the cinema to watch the movie, you're about to finish that story, how did they feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Obviously, I mean look my children have seen me come back from jail and all that to build this new life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "A tweet here from Sam Gustin in Time Magazine, a critical unanswered question comment on depiction that he remained on SCC deal, why do you that if true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "It's not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Time Magazine", "SCC"], "PERSON": ["Sam Gustin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "But it wasn't about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "It changed -- it wasn't like that really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Madden"]}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Did you feel guilt about all the people he went to prison because you basically wiped yourself up and ratted on him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Not Steve Madden at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Have you spoken to him since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 740, "question": "How do you feel about that now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "It's a good question and there's two sides to that coin because, you know, what do you -- the part of that says, \"Well, I'm supposed to do the right thing and be an upstanding citizen and as crimes committed I should help bring those people to justice.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Could you do the same again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "I think the way I split that was in the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "No regrets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "It's not that I don't have regrets, of course I have regrets about it but I think I made -- I know that I made the right decision morally and unethically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "So the best thing to say is I would say to you, \"Piers, how long have you been in the market for a pen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "``", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "I'm on the pen for three months.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "I see you're looking for a pen for three months now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "And what type of pens do you typically use when you use a pen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I like a nice easy to use ballpoint pen or something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]